healthwise.net 2005-12-12

# Privacy Policy

******** This privacy policy pertains to the corporate Web site of Healthwise. ****

Healthwise respects your privacy. In order to provide you with timely information and excellent customer service, we record some information from the forms you complete at our site. Healthwise does not release, trade, or sell any individually identifiable information gathered from users of healthwise.org, informationtherapy.org, or the Healthwise Knowledgebase hosted site to people or organizations outside of Healthwise. Any information that we gather is protected from misappropriation and misuse. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes while at the site. Cookies make Web surfing easier by saving your name, address, and other demographic preferences for you. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find most major Web sites use cookies. 

The healthwise.org site utilizes cookies to collect aggregate usage data and also make your requests for Healthwise information easier. Once you fill in your name and contact information on a form, the cookie serves to automatically complete, or “auto-populate,” those same fields for you the next time you fill out a form at our site. 

We do not and cannot use cookies to retrieve any personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you. Cookies do not provide us with access to any credit card information. Most computer browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. 

**Opting-In for E-mail Information  
** When you opt-in to receive further information from Healthwise, Incorporated, we will use that information to send you future occasional informational updates. You may opt-in for more information from Healthwise by using the order forms at our site. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate security measures to safeguard the information we collect online. We use Secure Sockets Layers (SSL)—the industry standard—for our online shopping cart service. SSL encrypts your order information into a highly indecipherable code before it travels over the Internet. ****

**Unsubscribing from Our Database** **  
** If you wish to be removed from our database (unsubscribe), simply unsubscribe to a Healthwise e-mail or contact us at [moreinfo@healthwise.org](mailto:moreinfo@healthwise.org). We will fulfill your request. 

**Notice of Change**  
Healthwise’s privacy policy is subject to change without notice. At any time, you may visit our Web site to read the most current policy. If you would like to contact Healthwise about our privacy policy, please e-mail us at [moreinfo@healthwise.org](mailto:moreinfo@healthwise.org). We will respond to your comments or questions within ten business days.
